https://sprowstonmethodist.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy HomePrivacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://sprowstonmethodist.org.uk.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
There are no facilities visitors to add comments / contact details on this site therefore no personal details are collected
Media
There are no facilities for visitors to add media on this site therefore no personal details are collected
Cookies
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
We do not share any personal data with anyone
How long we retain your data
We do not collect any personal data
What rights you have over your data
You can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.  To do this contact us stating what needs to be deleted.
GDPR- Privacy Notice
Recent Posts
Pastoral Letter – East Anglia District
Chair of the District – Revd. Julian M. Pursehouse October 2020
Pastoral Letter – East Anglia District Chair of the District – Revd. Julian M. Pursehouse September 2020
Fund for Human Need
Pastoral Letter – East Anglia District Chair of the District – Revd. Julian M. Pursehouse August 2020
Pastoral Letter – East Anglia District Chair of the District – Revd. Julian M. Pursehouse 08:07:2020
Previous Posts Previous Posts
Select Month
October 2020
September 2020
August 2020
July 2020
June 2020
May 2020
January 2016
Worship Service for use at home, click on the iconNext meeting: Cancelled for the forseeable future Messy Science Link  lots of things to try at home.
Trypraying is for those who are not religious and don’t do church.Sprowston Community Churches
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
